I closed the gate.
我把门关上过
I can break through.
我就可以再次冲破它
What are you doing?
你在干什么?
I need food for my battery.
我需要食物给我充电
You had a fully charged battery. You didn't make a dent.
你本来是充满电的 却连个凹痕都没留下
No. We're not getting through that thing, whatever it is, not this way at least.
我们没法穿越这个东西 不管这是什么 至少以这种方式不行
We have to.
我们必须要穿越
We don't even know if Holly's on the other side.
我们甚至都不知道 霍莉是否在另一边
The trail could've gone cold for a million reasons.
可能有成千上万个原因导致线索中断
Battery.
电池
Anything else?
还有别的吗?
Hey! I... No, I don't have anything else.
嘿!不 我没有别的了
I was packing for a party of one, a party of me.
我只带了一个人的行装 我自己的
You're lucky I'm sharing with you.
我愿意跟你分享 你已经很幸运了
Try it.
试试看吧
You might like it.
说不定你会喜欢呢
We gotta go.
我们得走了
El?
艾尔?
You okay?
你没事吧?
What's wrong? You all right?
怎么了?你没事吧?
Will, Robin, I need you to answer me.
威尔、罗宾 我需要你们回答我
I'm not mad. I just need to know you're safe.
我没生气 我只需要知道你们平安无事
Shit.
该死
- Is that, uh... - Yeah.
- 那是不是... - 是的
You think she saw us?
她看到我们了吗?
Yeah.
是的
Get in.
上车
I told you, I explicitly told you,
我告诉过你 我明确地告诉过你了
I didn't want him going anywhere that's not safe.
我不想要他去任何不安全的地方
And not only did you take him, you cut off all communication.
你不仅带他去了 还切断了所有通讯
Yes, I mean, in retrospect, that was a bit inconsiderate.
是的 回想起来 这么做的确有点考虑不周
Inconsiderate?
考虑不周?
We really should've left a note.
我们真的应该留个字条的
Is this funny to you?
你觉得这件事很好笑吗?
Oh. Sorry. It must be my tone.
对不起 一定是我的语气
My mother says I sound perpetually insincere.
我妈妈说我听起来总是假惺惺的
Okay, this is my son's life you're playing with.
好吧 你在玩弄的可是我儿子的生命
My son.
我的儿子
So next time I say I do not want him leaving my side,
所以下次我说我不想要他离开我身边
that means I don't want him leaving my goddamn side.
意思就是 我不想要他离开我该死的身边
I'm right here, Mom.
我就在这里 妈妈
You know, you can talk to me, right?
你知道你可以跟我聊的 对吧?
And I'm not a kid anymore.
而且我已经不是小孩子了
Will, I am still your mother.
威尔 我还是你的妈妈
- Doesn't mean you know what you're doing. - What?
- 这不代表你知道自己在做什么 - 什么?
Your plan? It... It sucked.
你的计划?
I'm sorry, but it did.
很抱歉 但的确如此
You only liked it because it was safe,
你喜欢这个计划只是因为它很安全
but we don't have time for safe, not anymore.
但我们没时间管安全 已经没时间了
We have to act, and we have to take risks, and thank God we did.
我们必须采取行动 必须冒上风险 幸好我们这么做了
Because my plan, it... it actually worked.
因为我的计划真的成功了
I spied on Vecna and tapped back into the hive mind,
我监视了维克那 重新接入了集体意识
and we found out that Holly was just the beginning.
我们发现 霍莉只是个开始
Vecna is gonna take more kids.
维克那会掳走更多孩子
I don't know why or what he wants to do with them,
我不知道为什么 或是他要对他们做什么
but now we know something we can use against him, his next target.
但我们现在知道了 能对付他的东西 他的下一个目标
So next time you order me to stay by your side, I wouldn't count on it.
所以下次你命令我 呆在你身边时 不要抱太大希望
But, as I said, in the future, we will try to leave a note.
但是就像我说的 未来我们会尽量留张字条
We should go. We have to stop Vecna. We don't have much time.
我们该走了 我们必须要阻止维克那 时间不多了
- Ready for the biosphere? - Yes, I am.
- 准备好制作生物圈了吗? - 是的
Okay. Think about the difference between land and water.
好的 想一想陆地和水之间的区别
Okay, got it. Thank you!
好的 知道了 谢谢!
Hey!
嘿!
You still thinking about your parents?
你还在想你的父母吗?
Yeah.
对
They are in the very best possible hands, Holly, I assure you.
他们在接受最好的治疗 霍莉 我向你保证这一点
And I'm told that they are improving with each hour that passes.
我听说他们的状况每小时都在好转
As soon as they're healed, they'll join us here.
一旦他们痊愈 就会加入我们
I... I know.
我知道
- It's just-- - You wish to be with them.
- 只是... - 你想和他们在一起
I understand.
我明白
But you cannot offer them comfort in Hawkins, Holly.
但是在霍金斯 你无法给他们提供安慰 霍莉
The only comfort they have is knowing you are here, safe.
他们唯一的安慰 就是知道你在这里 安全无虞
With me.
和我在一起
Safe from the monsters.
远离怪物们
I thought blackberries might cheer you up a little.
我想着黑莓可能会让你开心一点
They're your favorite, aren't they?
这是你最喜欢吃的 对吧?
How did you know?
你怎么知道
That they're my favorite?
这是我最喜欢吃的?
Oh, it's, uh...
就是...
It's just a hunch.
只是预感而已
I'm good with hunches.
我的预感很准
Perhaps tomorrow I'll make chocolate chip pancakes.
也许明天 我会做巧克力豆松饼
- He loves those. - Who does?
- 他很喜欢那些 - 谁很喜欢?
Your classmate, Derek.
你的同学德瑞克
Derek is coming here?
德瑞克要来这里?
You don't like Derek very much, do you?
你不是很喜欢德瑞克 是吧?
Should I just let the monsters eat him?
我应该让怪物把他吃掉吗?
No. No, you can't... you can't do that.
不 不行 你不能那样做
Well, how about this?
不如这样吧?
I will tell Derek
我会告诉德瑞克
that if he misbehaves, or if he hurts you in any way,
如果他表现不好 或是以任何方式伤害你
I will send him right back, and he can face those monsters on his own.
我就会马上送他回去 让他独自面对那些怪物
How does that sound?
你觉得怎么样?
I expect to be gone most of the day.
我预计今天大部分时间都不会回来
While I'm out, you'll have the whole house all to yourself.
我出去的时候 整个房子都是你一个人的
The whole house?
整个房子?
Everything which is mine is yours.
我拥有的一切也都属于你
But in return, I need you to promise me one thing.
但作为回报 我需要你答应我一件事
Something very important. Do you think you can do that?
一件很重要的事 你觉得你能做到吗?
Yeah.
好
You must never, under any circumstance, go out into the woods. Do you understand?
在任何情况下 你都不能到树林里去 你明白吗?
Is that where the monsters live?
那是怪物住的地方吗?
But they won't find you. That is, as long as you don't--
但它们不会找到你的 前提是 只要你别去...
Don't try to find them.
别去找它们
You know, I'm very glad I saved you first.
我很高兴我先救了你
You're the brightest of them all.
你是他们当中最聪明的人
Oh, and if you don't mind, bring my mail in, won't you?
如果你不介意的话 把我的信拿进去 好吗?
How did you know?
你怎么知道的?
A hunch.
预感
Base, Alpha one checking in.
基地 阿尔法一号报告情况
We're arrived at checkpoint H, H for Hercules.
我们到了H检查站 H代表赫拉克勒斯
No sign of freak.
没有怪胎的踪迹
We'll recon this area, then proceed to next checkpoint. Over.
我们会侦察这个区域 然后前往下一个检查站 完毕
Alpha 1, Base. Acknowledge your location at Hercules. Over.
阿尔法一号 基地确认你们的位置在H 完毕
Alpha 1, out.
阿尔法一号 结束通话
Recon?
侦察?
Meaning, I take a leak,
意思是我撒泡尿
and you guys take five.
你们休息五分钟
You heard the man. Smoke 'em if you got 'em.
你们都听到他说的了 休息一下吧
Some jackass messing with the wall, Lieutenant?
某个混蛋在墙上搞破坏了 中尉?
Some jackass, yeah.
某个混蛋 没错
But not one of ours.
但不是我们的人
Come on.
来吧
Get on the hedgehog.
上刺猬车
Yes, sir.
走吧
Come up! Come up!
上来!
Base, Alpha 1, we're taking enemy fire. Need backup and air cover now.
基地 阿尔法一号 我们遭敌方攻击 需要立即支援和空中掩护
Okay.
好吧
It looks like Robin sent up the Bat-Signal.
看来是罗宾发出了求救的蝙蝠信号
Hey. I'm so sorry.
嘿 真的很遗憾
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
- 你没事吧? - 对
Here.
来吧
Holy shit.
我的妈呀
Yep.
对
Bike crash. Flew headfirst into a light post.
骑车出了车祸 人飞了出去 头先撞到了灯柱上
Look, I'm sorry about missing the crawl, about everything.
听着 很抱歉 我错过了潜行 还有一切
It's not your fault. Don't beat yourself up.
不是你的错 不用自责的
Yeah, looks like he already did.
对 看来他已经自责过了
- Is that broken? - I dunno.
- 骨头断了吗? - 我不知道
- Let me... - Don't touch it. Why--
- 让我... - 别碰 为什么...
- I wasn't... I wanted to... - You were going to.
- 我不是...我只是想看... - 你本来要碰了
Hey, this isn't a social call, kiddos. Let's go.
嘿 我们不是来闲聊的 孩子们 走了
Derek?
德瑞克?
Derek Turnbow?
德瑞克·特恩鲍?
As in the Turnbow family? Like Turnbow Realty?
特恩鲍家族?特恩鲍地产那个?
The one and only.
正是他没错
Whole family's a menace.
全家人都是祸害
How can you be sure?
你怎么能确定?
Sure that Derek's the next target?
确定德瑞克是下一个目标?
Because I saw.
因为我看到了
I've learned that when I'm close enough to the hive mind,
我发现了 当我足够接近集体意识时
I can tap into it, into Vecna's mind.
我可以利用它进入维克那的思想
I can see who he's targeting.
我能看到他的目标是谁
The first time it happened, I saw through Holly's eyes
事情第一次发生的时候 我是从霍莉的眼睛里看的
the same day she was taken.
她在同一天就被掳走了
And this morning, it happened again.
今天早上 又发生了
Only this time, I wasn't Holly.
只不过这一次 我不是霍莉了
- What the hell? - I was someone else.
- 什么鬼? - 我是另一个人
- Watch where you're going, dipshit. - Suck a fat one!
- 走路小心点 蠢蛋 - 有多远滚多远!
I was Derek Turnbow. I'm positive.
我就是德瑞克·特恩鲍 我很确定
Hold on. I'm a little lost.
等等 我没跟上
Shocking.
真令人震惊
Were you seeing through the eyes of... of Vecna or of Derek?
你是透过维克那的眼睛 还是德瑞克的眼睛看到的?
Both.
两个人都是
I... I was Vecna,
我是维克那
but inside Derek's mind.
但在德瑞克的脑子里
Vecna's like a psychic serial killer.
维克那是一个有超能力的连环杀手
He stalks his victims, but he does it by invading their minds.
他跟踪他的受害者 但是通过侵入他们的思想来做到的
That's what he did with Chrissy and Max.
他就是这样对付克丽丝和麦克斯的
Yeah, but the way he's doing it this time is different.
对 但他这次的做法不一样
We did some digging at the hospital. It turns out that before he took Holly,
我们在医院做了一番调查 发现维克那在掳走霍莉之前
Vecna stalked her.
跟踪过她
But... he didn't appear as Vecna. He appeared as Henry.
但是...他不是以维克那 而是以亨利的形象出现的
As a friend.
作为朋友出现的
We think he was trying to earn her trust.
我们认为他是想要赢得她的信任
Now, why he went to all that trouble, we don't know.
我们不知道他为什么要费那么大功夫
But I highly doubt his long-term goal is friendship.
但我高度怀疑 他的长期目标是建立友谊
Whatever it is, whatever he's planning,
不管是什么 不论他在计划什么
we have to stop him.
我们都必须阻止他
And we have to save Derek.
我们得救下德瑞克
The Turnbows live here.
特恩鲍家住在这里
We wait in a van across the street.
我们在马路对面的面包车里等着
As soon as they're asleep, we move in, we grab Derek,
他们一睡着 我们就进去 把德瑞克抓出来
and we take him to here,
我们把他带到这里
the McCorkle farm. It's completely isolated. It's abandoned.
麦考克农场 完全与世隔绝的被遗弃的农场
The only thing is, we need to make sure he doesn't see us or know where he is.
唯一的问题是 我们得确保 他看不到我们 也不知道自己在哪里
So we'll need to blindfold him.
我们就需要蒙住他的眼睛
Wait. Hold on. What?
等等 等一下 什么?
So that Vecna can't find him.
这样维克那就找不到他了
Yeah. What, and Mom, you're okay with just kidnapping a child?
对 什么 还有妈妈 你觉得绑架一个孩子没问题吗?
No, we're saving a child via kidnapping.
不 我们是通过绑架来拯救一个孩子
And yeah, it's fine,
是的 没问题
I think.
我觉得是吧
Yes. Now's not the time to play it safe, Jonathan.
对 现在不是保守行事的时候 乔纳森
If I may,
如果我可以插一句的话
though I'm not morally opposed to any of this, there are a few holes.
虽然我在道德上 并不反对这些 但有几个漏洞
Yeah. Like what if Derek falls asleep before the Demogorgon attacks him?
对 比方说万一德瑞克 在被魔王攻击之前睡着了怎么办?
That's one.
这是一个漏洞
Or what if Derek wakes up before we grab him, alerts his family?
或者万一德瑞克在被我们抓走之前 醒了过来 通知了他的家人怎么办?
- We'll go to jail. - There's another.
我们会坐牢的
But the third and most gaping hole is
但第三个、也是最大的漏洞是
even if by some miracle this plan even works,
就算奇迹出现 这个计划能行得通
Holly's still missing.
霍莉依然失踪
Hop and El, still MIA.
霍珀和艾尔还是下落不明
This doesn't bring us any closer to finding Vecna.
并不能帮我们 更接近找到维克那的目标
This plan just buys us and Derek some time.
这个计划 只能给我们和德瑞克多争取一些时间
That's it.
仅此而已
Not necessarily.
不一定
There might be a way.
也许有办法
A way to save Derek and find Holly.
让我们既能拯救德瑞克又能找到霍莉
This is Derek.
这是德瑞克
And this is the rest of the Turnbow family.
这是特恩鲍一家剩下的成员
We're gonna need to recruit someone that the family trusts,
我们需要招募一个这家人信任的人
someone that can gain access to the house.
一个能进入他们家房子的人
This person will knock the family out.
这个人会把全家人都弄晕
Then we'll extract the family.
然后我们把家人从房子里撤走
Knock them out?
把他们弄晕?
Well, safely. With sleeping pills or something.
好吧 以安全的方式 安眠药之类的
I might know where we could get some benzos.
我可能知道在哪里可以弄到安定类药
Those things could knock an elephant on its ass.
那玩意能把大象都迷晕
Perfect. That way if Vecna spies,
完美 这样 如果维克那去刺探
he'll just assume Derek is fast asleep in bed.
他就会假定德瑞克是在床上睡着了
He'll send his Demos to grab him.
他会派魔王去抓他
Only he won't find Derek. He'll find us.
只不过 他不会找到德瑞克 他会找到我们
And we'll be ready.
而我们会做好准备
We'll get Murray to supply us with the traps.
我们会让穆雷给我们弄些陷阱
We'll burn the sucker. Send him scampering home to its master,
我们火烧那个蠢货 让它跑回它的主人身边
but not before we stick him with one of these.
但在那之前 我们在它身上安插一个这个
We'll track the Demo across the Upside Down
我们会在躁点面包车上 在颠倒世界里追踪魔王
in the Squawk van just like we did with Hopper.
就像我们追踪霍珀一样
And if we're lucky, the Demo will lead us back to its lair,
如果我们幸运的话 魔王会带我们回到它的巢穴
to Vecna,
找到维克那
to Holly.
找到霍莉
Holes?
漏洞?
Cause what would they say
因为他们要是知道了会怎么说呢?
Henry?
亨利?
Derek, if this is you, it's not funny, you barf bag!
德瑞克 如果是你 这一点都不好笑 死猪!
"I need your help."
“我需要你的帮助
"Meet me at the X."
在画X的地方和我碰头”
"Henry."
“亨利”
East.
东
Move aside. Coming through! Make way, please!
让开 我要通过!请让路!
You're gonna be okay, man. Just hang in there.
你会没事的 坚持住
Sir!
长官!
Orders?
命令?
Find who did this.
找出是谁干的
Bring them to me.
把这个人带过来
And I will disembowel the son of a bitch!
我会把这个混蛋开膛破肚!
Sir!
长官!
Let's go! Move out!
走吧!出发!
Got that Humvee hid pretty good.
那辆悍马车藏得很好
If they don't know it's missing yet, they will soon.
如果他们还不知道 它不见了 他们很快就会发现的
Got more birds.
又有更多飞机来了
They all got those speakers, whatever they are.
他们都装了大喇叭 不管这玩意儿到底是什么
I don't know how, but...
我不知道怎么做到的 但是...
Seems like our military friends found your kryptonite.
我们的军人朋友们 似乎是找到你打败你的氪石了
Hey.
嘿
Any movement from our guest?
客人有什么动静吗?
Better not be brain-dead.
最好别是脑死亡了
He peed on it.
他尿在上面了
What?
什么?
That soldier.
那个士兵
You said he peed on the big wall.
你说他尿在那堵大墙上了
Yeah, no, I heard what you said.
对 不是 我听到你说了什么
I just don't know why you're talking about it.
我只是不知道你为什么要说这个
Maybe he knows what it is...
也许他知道那是什么...
Or how to get through it.
或是如何穿过去
That's highly doubtful.
这很难说
What he will know, though,
但他会知道的
is the schedule for the next supply convoy,
是下一个补给车队的日程安排
which is our way out of this hellhole.
这就是我们离开这个地狱的出路
What happens then?
那之后会发生什么?
We go back, we tell everybody what we saw, and we... we...
我们回去 告诉大家我们看到了什么 然后我们...
Make a new plan.
制定新的计划
The others? You think they'll know how to get through the wall?
其他人?你觉得 他们会知道怎么穿过墙吗?
I don't know. Maybe, yeah.
我不知道 也许吧 是的
They won't.
他们不会知道的
We'll be back to the first square.
我们就又回到了圆形的点
- Square one. - He peed on it.
- 原点 - 他尿在上面了
Even if he knows something,
就算他知道些什么
he's been trained to resist interrogation.
他接受过抵抗拷问的训练
The Russians took two weeks trying to break me,
俄国人花了两周时间试图击垮我
and they still couldn't.
他们还是没能做到
We don't have two weeks. We don't have two hours.
我们没有两周的时间 我们甚至没有两个小时
Convoy information, I might be able to get out of him.
我也许能从他身上拷问出车队信息
Classified information? That's not gonna happen.
机密信息?那是不可能的
With my help, it will.
有我的帮助 就能做到
Oh, yeah, I'm sorry.
哦 对 对不起
I forgot about your extensive training in interrogation tactics.
我忘了你还接受过审讯策略的训练
My battery's charged.
我的电池充满电了
I don't see how that helps us.
我看不出这对我们有什么帮助
- I can break him. - El...
- 我可以击垮他 - 艾尔...
Twenty minutes.
20分钟
You get to ask him about the convoy.
你可以问他车队的事
You get what you want,
你得到你想要的
then I get what I want.
然后我得到我想要的
Compromise. "C-O-M-promise." Remember?
妥协的意思是“合作并承诺”
Halfway happy.
幸福的半路
Get me outta here! Get me the hell outta here!
放我出去!该死的放我出去!
You're a stubborn punk-ass. You know that, right?
你是个固执的窝囊废 你知道的吧?
Einstein-Rosen bridges,
爱因斯坦-罗森桥
more commonly known as wormholes,
更常见的名字是虫洞
are often depicted in an hourglass-like shape,
经常被描绘成沙漏状
such as this.
就像这样
While the existence of wormholes is entirely theoretical,
虽然虫洞完全只是在理论上存在
they have captured the fascination
它们还是吸引了科学家
of scientists and science fiction writers alike.
以及科幻作家极大的兴趣
Can anyone tell me why that is?
谁能告诉我这是为什么?
Come on. This is easy. Just...
拜托 很简单的 就...
What's neat about wormholes?
虫洞有什么妙处?
Okay. Erica.
好吧 艾瑞卡
Wormholes are neat
虫洞很妙
because they allow matter to travel between galaxies or dimensions
是因为它们让物质 可以跨越星系或维度旅行
without crossing the space between.
而不需要穿越中间的空间
Yes. Exactly right.
对 完全正确
Again.
又说对了
And, uh, just think of all the places mankind could go.
还有 就设想一下 人类都能去什么地方吧
Another galaxy.
另一个星系
Another time, even.
甚至是另一个时间
So why aren't we doing it now?
那我们为什么不现在就去做呢?
If wormholes did exist, they would be extraordinarily unstable.
如果虫洞真的存在 它们会极度不稳定
Their enormous gravitational force would rip them apart
它们巨大的引力 会在它们形成的那一刻
at the very moment they formed. Now...
就把它们撕成碎片 好了...
You have 60 seconds to explain why you interrupted my favorite class.
你们有60秒的时间解释 为什么打断了我最喜欢的课
Erica, this is really serious.
艾瑞卡 事情很严重
57, 56...
57、56...
It's hard to explain everything in 56 seconds.
好吧 很难在56秒内解释清楚一切
But basically, everything went bad at the crawl last night.
但基本上昨晚的潜行彻底搞砸了
Wouldn't know. I wasn't invited.
我不会知道的 没人邀请我
That's why I'm ex--
所以我才...
That's why I'm explaining.
所以我才要给你解释
Things went bad at the crawl, and a lot of stuff happened,
潜行搞砸了 发生了很多事
and now we think Tina's little brother's in trouble.
现在我们觉得 蒂娜的弟弟遇上麻烦了
That literally makes no sense.
这根本就说不通
And even if it did, why would I care that Dipshit Derek is in trouble?
就算说得通 我为什么要在乎 蠢蛋德瑞克有没有遇上麻烦?
You're just gonna have to trust us, okay?
你必须要相信我们 好吗?
And to help Derek, we're gonna need you to get us into the Turnbow house.
为了帮助德瑞克 我们需要你带我们进入特恩鲍家
- Tonight. - Not possible.
- 今晚 - 不可能
Of course it is. Make plans to hang out with Tina.
当然可能 计划一下和蒂娜一起玩就行了
- Tina and I don't hang. - You hang nonstop. She's your best friend.
- 蒂娜和我不在一起玩 - 你们一直在玩 她是你最好的朋友
- Was. - Was?
- 曾经是 - 曾经是?
- We are now enemies. - Enemies?
- 我们现在是敌人了 - 敌人?
- Arch. - Since when?
- 死敌 - 什么时候开始的?
Since PE class 12 days ago.
12天前上完体育课之后
Then apologize for what happened in PE class 12 days ago.
那就为12天前体育课上发生的事道歉
- No can do. - Yes, can do.
- 做不到 - 做得到的
All you have to do is use your mouth to form a word that rhymes with "starry."
你只需要用你的嘴 摆出一个和“推不起”押韵的词
I'd rather learn about wormholes than apologize to Tina
我更宁愿去了解虫洞 我才不想向蒂娜道歉
and help you all save Dipshit Derek.
或是帮助你们 拯救蠢蛋德瑞克 对不起
Time's up.
时间到了
This isn't about saving Derek. It's about saving Holly.
这不是为了救德瑞克 是为了救霍莉
Vecna took her.
维克那把她掳走了
And yeah, now he's after Dipshit Derek. But we have a plan.
是的 现在他的目标 是蠢蛋德瑞克 但我们有个计划
A plan to both save Dipshit Derek and find Holly.
一个既能拯救蠢蛋德瑞克 又能找到霍莉的计划
But the plan is...
但这个计划...
It's a bit insane.
有点疯狂
But after it's over,
但在计划结束后
I don't think Tina's gonna wanna talk to you ever again.
我觉得蒂娜再也不会想和你说话了
Well, why the hell didn't you just start with that?
那你为什么不一开始就跟我说这个?
Hi, Doris.
嗨 多丽丝
- You are just psychic, I'm telling you. - I am. Thank you, baby.
- 我跟你说 你就是有超能力 - 我是有 谢谢你 宝贝
- Thank you. - Y'all go on back there.
- 谢谢 - 你们都到后面去吧
Who's Mrs. Massey?
梅西太太是谁?
My sweet granny who fell down a flight of stairs
我善良的奶奶 她从楼梯上摔了下来
and broke nearly every bone in her frail old body.
几乎摔断了 她脆弱的身体里的每一根骨头
Oh God. I'm sorry.
天啊 我很遗憾
Don't be too sorry. She's not my real granny.
不用太遗憾 她不是我真正的奶奶
I use her name so I can visit Vickie.
我是用她的名字来找薇琪的
I know it sounds unethical, but I always bring her cookies,
我知道听起来不道德 但我总是给她带饼干
and I think Mrs. Massey loves me more than her own family at this point.
我觉得现在梅西太太 爱我已经超过爱她自己的家人了
More importantly, she has got, like, a mondo stash of benzos,
更重要的是 她有一大堆安定类药物
and her nurse is a slacker who never locks the medicine cabinet.
她的护士是个懒鬼 药柜从不上锁
...This story I heard.
...我听到的这个故事
- Shit. - Oh!
该死
- What... What are we doing? - Hiding.
- 我们在做什么? - 躲起来
- Hiding? Right. Why? - Down.
- 躲起来?对了 为什么? - 蹲下
Jesus, she talks so much.
天啊 她话真是太多了
- I know. I'm a hypocrite. - I...
- 我知道 我是个伪君子 - 我...
We have to go!
我们得走了!
I promised Vickie that I would take her to Enzo's tonight,
我答应过薇琪 我今晚会带她去恩佐餐厅
and now I can't, obviously,
现在我显然不能赴约了
meaning I have to ditch her again
意味着我必须再次放她鸽子
for reasons that she just can't understand.
因为一些她无法理解的原因
A massive fight will ensue, and we'll never make it to my fake granny's room.
一次大吵会接踵而至 我们永远都去不了我假奶奶的房间
I can't be the reason Wheeler's plan fails.
我不能成为 导致惠勒计划失败的原因
- Okay? - Okay.
- 好吗? - 好的
Shoot. Stay low.
该死 别起身
You know, you could always just kiss her again.
你知道 你完全可以再亲她一次的
I knew that was your goddamn bowl cut.
我就知道那是你那个该死的碗盖头
Yeah, I mean, they're not that popular anymore.
对 我的意思是 这发型现在已经不那么流行了
Did I look like I knew what I was doing at least?
我至少看起来 像不像是知道自己在做什么?
I mean, yeah. To me.
我想说是的 对我来说是
I guess that's something.
我想这也算数吧
So, how did you know that, with Vickie, right?
所以你怎么知道她想要 她是叫薇琪 对吧?
How did you know that Vickie wanted to...
你怎么知道薇琪想要...
- Make out? - ...To date?
- 亲热? - ...约会?
Signals?
信号?
Yeah, you know, like a brush of the knee, a bump of the elbow, a shared look.
对 你懂的 就比如摩擦一下膝盖 手肘轻碰 一个心照不宣的眼神
It all just kind of accrued, like a snowball rolling down a hill,
都是逐渐累积起来的 就像滚下山的一个雪球
until it was obvious.
直到变得很明显
How obvious?
有多明显?
Let's say the, uh, snowball became an avalanche.
这么说吧 那个雪球变成了雪崩
Oh God, that looks awful.
天啊 看起来糟透了
Sure does.
必须的
And he's in the same wing as my fake granny.
他和我的假奶奶住在同一个侧翼
- Meaning? - Same slacker nurse.
- 什么意思? - 也是那个懒鬼护士管的
Jackpot.
中大奖了
Jesus, we could knock out half of Hawkins with this shit.
天啊 用这玩意 我们可以把霍金斯一半的人都迷晕
- Okay, load me up. - Okay.
- 好了 给我装上吧 - 好的
Okay, so, I couldn't get any ethanol,
好了 我没能弄到酒精
but I was able to scrounge up a gallon of acetone.
但我凑到了3.8升丙酮
Be very careful.
千万要小心
You smoke a Virginia Slim too close to this stuff, it'll catch fire, okay?
要是在离它太近的地方抽烟 这东西会点着的 好吗?
Snare wire, various gauges.
各种规格的捕兽钢丝
A creepy, child-sized CPR dummy.
一个诡异的 儿童大小的心肺复苏假人
Its purpose a mystery to me.
它的用处对我来说是个谜
Shotgun shells, per our lovely lady's request.
霰弹枪弹 应这位漂亮女士的要求
Three 20-packs of water balloons. Purpose also a mystery.
每包20个装的水球 共三包 这个的用处也是个谜
But I did take the liberty of selecting the grenade style
但我确实擅自挑选了手榴弹风格
as it felt thematically appropriate.
因为感觉这个主题会很合适
Do keep those far away from...
一定要让那些远离...
These 3,000 feet of barbed wire.
这914米长的铁丝网
Some sparkling new spark plugs for Bilbo Baggins.
给比尔博·巴金斯准备的 一些闪闪发亮的全新火花塞
Spark plugs, that's it?
火花塞 就这些?
I'm also giving out free hugs.
我也会提供免费的拥抱
- You didn't get the turbocharger? - No.
- 你没搞到涡轮增压器? - 没有
- The suspension kit?
- 悬挂系统套件?
- The aerodynamic spoiler? - No.
- 空气动力扰流板? - 没有
It wasn't a goddamn Christmas list, Murray.
这可不是该死的圣诞心愿清单 穆雷
That's exactly what it was.
这完完全全就是
And the fact that Santa Murray scrounged all this up in a single afternoon
而且圣诞老人穆雷 一个下午就搜刮到了所有这些
and smuggled it into what is likely the most heavily secured location
并把它偷运进了极有可能是除了白宫
outside of the White House, Fort Knox, and Area 51
诺克斯堡和51区外 戒备最为森严的地方
is a goddamn Christmas miracle.
就是个该死的圣诞奇迹
So, count your blessings,
所以你就好好知足感恩
hang some mistletoe, pucker up,
挂上槲寄生 撅起嘴来
and kiss my jolly ass!
亲吻我胖乎乎的屁股吧!
Thank you for the spark plugs.
谢谢你的火花塞
- What are you doing? - You gonna help or just stand there?
- 你在做什么? - 你要帮忙还是就站在那里?
I'd rather not herniate a disc over a lost cause.
我不想为徒劳无功的事 搞到椎间盘突出
Yeah, that's the attitude.
对 这态度就对了
This van once stalled out chugging up Pickett Road
这面包车有一次 在皮克特路爬坡时都熄火了
like it was the Little Engine That Couldn't.
就像是《小火车头做不到》
It's not fast enough to keep up with a Demo without serious modifications.
速度跟不上魔王的 没有经过大幅改装肯定不行
What the hell do you think I'm doing? Modifying.
那你以为我是在干什么?改装
A lighter van is a faster van.
轻一些的面包车就能快一些
If we're just tracking, we don't need half of the crap in here.
如果我们只是追踪 这里的破烂有一半都不需要
Speaking of, can you go empty the window washer fluid?
说起来 你能到前面去 把车窗清洗液倒掉吗?
The window washer fluid. That'll do it. Good job, Steven.
车窗清洗液 这样就成了 干得好 史蒂夫
We should go back to the agreement from yesterday.
也许我们应该 回到我们昨天同意的协议
- What agreement? - The no-talking agreement.
- 什么协议? - 不许说话协议
What are you doing? Henderson, I'm using that.
你在干什么?亨德森 那个我要用的
Hey. You little shit!
嘿 你这个小混蛋!
I said I'm using that, man.
我说了那个我要用的 朋友
What are you-- Yo, hey!
你在干什么...哟 嘿!
Get off the Beamer, man. Get off!
从宝马上下来 朋友 快下来!
You were right. For once.
你总算说对了一次
We don't need half the crap in there for our mission.
我们这次的任务 你那里面一半的垃圾都用不上
In fact, the only thing we really need is a telemetry tracker,
事实上 我们唯一真正需要的是遥测追踪器
which I can affix to any vehicle.
我可以把它固定在任何车辆上
Henderson...
亨德森
Don't you touch her.
不许碰我的车!
Henderson!
亨德森!
Henderson, I'm dead serious.
亨德森 我是认真的
- No talking. - Wait, wait, wait!
- 不许说话 - 等等!
Hey, hey! What are you...
嘿!你这是在...
No! What the...
不!搞什么...
- Okay, transmitter? - Yeah.
- 好了 发射器? - 是
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Children. Children.
哇 孩子们
- What are we doing? - What does it look like?
- 我们在做什么? - 看起来像是在做什么?
Well, it looks like you're loading my telemetry tracker into a shotgun shell
好吧 你们看起来 是把我的遥测追踪器装进霰弹枪弹里
in what I presume are the hopes
我假设你们是希望将子弹
of firing it into an interdimensional being.
射入一个跨维度的生物体内
You told me that these transmitters
你告诉我说这些发射器
were designed specifically to withstand harsh conditions.
是专门为了承受恶劣的环境而设计的
Blasting it out of a shotgun into some beast isn't a harsh condition.
用霰弹枪把它 射入野兽体内并不是恶劣环境
It's deadly.
而是致命的
If the heat from the exploding gunpowder doesn't destroy the transmitter,
如果火药爆炸 产生的热量没有摧毁发射器
the force from the recoil will.
后坐力也会摧毁掉它
And is that a fact
这是一个事实
or... a theory?
还是理论?
A theory.
一个理论
Let's test it then.
那我们来测试一下吧
What's her deal today, huh?
所以她今天是怎么回事?
Her deal?
她怎么回事?
Yeah.
是呀
Her sister is missing. Her parents almost died.
她妹妹失踪了 她的父母差点死了
- Sure, sure. But what about, you know? - No, I don't.
- 当然了 但是那个呢?你懂的 - 不 我不懂
Coltrane, Love Supreme.
约翰·柯川 《崇高的爱》
- Did you give it a whirl? - Yeah.
- 你尝试听了吗? - 是的
- And? - It was very nice.
- 然后呢? - 非常好
- What? Thank you?
- 什么?谢谢你?
Christ, man! You haven't done it yet, have you?
老天!你还没下手 是不是?
I thought you were desperate, that things were stagnating,
我以为你很绝望 情况停滞不前
that your mating competition was making moves.
你的交配竞争对手正在采取行动
- Whoa! - Hey!
- 哇! - 嘿!
Whatever you two are conspiring about back there, please do it later.
不管你们两个 在后面密谋什么 请晚点再做
Our apologies, milady.
抱歉了 尊敬的小姐
And hurry up. We don't have all day.
抓紧点 我们赶时间呢
Why the delay?
为什么要拖延?
Have you forgotten the fact
你是不是忘了
that her sister is missing and her parents are in the hospital?
她妹妹失踪、她的父母住院的事?
Could one ask for better conditions?
还有比这更好的条件吗?
The death of a loved one is the painful but necessary reminder
至亲的死是痛苦但必要的提醒
that life is delicate, precious,
表明生命是脆弱而珍贵的
that one must not take those around us for granted,
绝不能把周围的人看作是理所当然
that one must strengthen bonds.
必须要加强纽带
I mean, hell, man,
我是说 天啊 朋友
the two of you were brought together by shared trauma in the first place.
你们两个最开始 就是因为共同的创伤才走到一起的
This is the stuff of fate, of destiny.
这是命运的安排 是命中注定
So, if not for your sake, then for mine.
所以如果不是为了你 就当为了我吧
Grow some balls and get it over with already.
勇敢一点 赶紧去做完了事吧
Hey! If you don't shut up right now, Santa,
嘿!如果你不立刻闭嘴 圣诞老人
I swear to God I will shoot this tracker into your potato sacks.
我对天发誓 我会把这追踪器射入你的囊中
I'm a good enough shot to hit any mark,
你知道我有足够的能力击中任何目标
no matter how small.
不管目标多小
Jesus.
天啊
Now set up my target.
现在就把我的靶子摆好
Okay.
好吧
Quite large, actually.
其实挺大的
My... potato sacks.
我的...
Well, would you look at that, Santa? Another miracle.
瞧瞧吧 圣诞老人 又是一个奇迹
At the very least,
至少
couldn't hurt her mood.
不会影响她的心情
Hey!
嘿!
How's the head?
你的头怎么样?
You'll get nothing out of me.
我什么都不会告诉你的
So if you're gonna kill me, get to it.
所以如果你想杀了我 就动手吧
It's tempting.
这主意很诱人
But no.
但是不行
Just need a little information, okay?
只需要一点点信息 好吗?
I need to know about that fleshy wall.
我需要知道那堵肉墙的事
Don't know a thing about it. I'm just a grunt.
我什么都不知道 我只是个步兵
A grunt?
步兵?
Is that funny to you?
你觉得这好笑吗?
Let me get this straight. You're telling me you just,
让我理理清楚 你是说你只是
like all the other boots on the ground, came to Hawkins to direct traffic
像其他地面部队一样 来霍金斯就是为了指挥交通
and save kitty cats out of trees.
把猫咪从树上救下来
- You're just a red, white, and blue grunt. - That's what I said.
- 你只是个美国大兵 - 我就是这个意思
I used to be a grunt.
我以前是也当过步兵
So I know the difference.
所以我知道其中的区别
You're something else.
你不一样
Some kind of special forces puke.
你是某种讨人厌的特种部队
I used to have to put up with guys like you in Nam.
我在越南的时候 也不得不忍受像你这样的人
Guys who cut the ears off enemy corpses,
会把敌人尸体上的耳朵割下来
make a necklace out of them.
做成项链的家伙
Pretty sick, you ask me.
你要问我的话 都是些病态的人
Grunt, my ass. You're one of Sullivan's attack dogs.
去你的鬼步兵吧 你是沙利文的一条攻击犬
You're the psychos he lets slip off the leash
你是他想去沙漠里
when he wants to, I don't know, go into the desert
为了追杀一个小女孩
and massacre a group of unarmed scientists all in the pursuit of one little girl.
屠杀一群手无寸铁的科学家时 会放出来的一个精神病
Little... Little girl?
小女孩?
She's a freak!
她是个怪胎!
She took down a helicopter just by looking at it.
她用一个眼神就击落了一架直升机
I had friends in that Huey, man.
那架直升机里有我的朋友
Oh my God! My heart is breaking for you.
哦 天啊!我真为你心碎
You, whoever you are, you just took out more of my guys,
不管你是谁 你刚刚干掉了我更多手下
so go to hell.
所以你下地狱去吧
I'm already there. Look around you.
我已经在地狱里了 看看你周围吧
I gotta tell you something about this old ex-grunt.
关于我这个老步兵 我得告诉你一件事
Those guys I killed, I'd kill them a hundred times over.
我杀的那些人 我会再杀他们一百次
I'd kill a thousand guys like you
我会杀一千个像你这样的人
to protect the one person that I love.
为了保护我爱的那一个人
All right.
好吧
So you don't know about the wall, huh?
所以你不知道墙的事?
Who does?
谁知道?
Dr. Kay?
凯博士?
- Who? - Kay.
- 谁? - 凯
The one that even Sullivan takes orders from.
那个就连沙利文也要听从的人
- Don't know who you're talking about. - Really?
- 不知道你在说谁 - 真的吗?
Then why'd you tell us her name?
那你为什么告诉我们她的名字?
What?
什么?
Her name. You told us her name.
她的名字 你告诉了我们她的名字
Us?
我们?
That little girl you're looking for?
你要找的那个小女孩?
She's rooting around in that tiny brain of yours as we speak.
她此刻正在你的小脑袋里翻箱倒柜呢
She can see everything.
她能看到一切
Everything you've ever thought, everything you've ever seen.
你想过的一切、你见到过的一切
So you might as well start talking.
所以你还是开始交代吧
'Cause if you don't give me answers, she'll find them.
因为如果你不回答 她也会找到答案
So why don't we save some time?
那我们为什么不节省点时间呢?
Where do I find Dr. Kay?
凯博士在哪里?
I... I don't know where she is.
我不知道她在哪里
You can lie to me all you want. You can't lie to her.
你想骗我就随意吧 你可骗不了她
- I'm not lying to you. - Yes, you are.
- 我没有骗你 - 是的 你就是在撒谎
You know this Dr. Kay. Where is Dr. Kay?
你知道这个凯博士 凯博士在哪里?
I don't know--
我不知道...
Is it really necessary to take these lashings from Kay in person?
真的有必要当面承受凯的指责吗?
Just shut up and drive, Akers.
闭嘴开车吧 艾克斯
There's a base in the Upside Down.
颠倒世界里有一个基地
Gable Ridge Road.
山墙岭路
- Gable Ridge Road Base. - What the hell is she doing to me?
- 山墙岭路基地 - 她到底在对我做什么?
I don't exactly know how it works, but I know it's probably not a good idea
我不知道具体原理 但我知道让她在里面翻找太久
What was this meeting about with you and the good doctor?
你和这位博士见面是什么原因?
The freak. She wants the freak. That's her mission. That's all I know.
怪胎 她想要那个怪胎 那是她的任务 我只知道这些
You have one more month, Lieutenant Colonel.
你还有一个月的时间 中校
Then I find someone else to lead this operation.
然后我就找别人来领导这次行动了
Thank you, ma'am.
谢谢你 女士
Akers, let's go.
艾克斯 走吧
There's a door at the end.
尽头有一扇门
Big, metal,
大门 金属的
like a vault.
就像金库
There's a door, a big door, secure door, down a corridor, down a hallway.
有一扇门 一扇加固的大门 沿着走廊的 在走廊尽头
- What's behind that door? - I don't know.
- 门后面是什么? - 我不知道
What's behind that door?
门后面是什么?
I told you I don't know. God!
我说了我不知道 天啊!
There's something back there. He doesn't want me to see.
后面有东西 他不想让我看到
- My head! My head! - Hey, I can make it stop.
- 我的头! - 嘿 我可以让它停止
What's behind the door?
门后面是什么?
Secret shit. I don't know. Just get the freak out, man.
秘密的东西 我不知道 快把怪胎给弄出去吧 伙计
I can make it stop, but you gotta tell me the truth.
我可以让它停止 但你得告诉我真相
What's behind that door?
门后面是什么?
Does it have something to do with the wall?
和墙有什么关系吗?
I told you I don't know.
我说过了我不知道
Come on! What's behind the door?!
拜托!门后面是什么?
I swear to God, I don't know!
我对天发誓 我不知道!
Just get her out of my head! Get her out of my head!
把她从我脑子里赶出去!把她赶走!
Hey, hey, hey!
嘿!
What the hell was that? What happened?
刚刚是怎么回事?怎么了?
El, are you all right? El?
艾尔 你没事吧?艾尔?
Kryptonite.
氪石
What?
什么?
I heard it behind the door, louder than before.
我在门后听到了 声音比以前都大
The doctor's keeping someone there,
博士在里面关了个人
someone powerful like me.
像我这样有超能力的人
It has to be.
一定是了
It has to be what?
一定是什么?
The military,
军队
they have him.
他们抓到他了
They have Vecna.
他们抓到了维克那
It doesn't make sense. Henry said never to go into the woods. Never, ever.
这说不通 亨利说了 不能到树林里去 永远都不能去
Why am I talking to you anyways?
总之 我为什么要跟你说话?
You're a pop star. What do you know about monsters?
你是流行歌星 你对怪物有多少了解?
What would you do?
你会怎么做?
Stupid.
笨蛋
It smells like ass in here, dipshit.
这里全都是屁股的味道 蠢蛋
Probably from all my farts.
很可能是因为我放了很多屁
Disgusting.
恶心
Mom wants you down for dinner.
妈妈叫你下楼吃饭
Mom can suck a fat one.
妈妈可以有多远滚多远了!
Hey!
嘿!
Tina! Give it back, Tina!
蒂娜!把它还给我 蒂娜!
Tina!
蒂娜!
How many times must I repeat myself? This home is not a playground.
我要重复多少次?这个家不是游乐场
Derek, wash up. Tina, get the door, and be polite.
德瑞克 去洗洗干净 蒂娜 去开门 礼貌一点
Unless it's a Mormon.
除非是摩门教徒
Or a Democrat.
或是民主党人
Listen, I know you probably hate me right now,
听着 我知道你现在可能恨我
but I thought you might want your favorite pie.
但我想着 你可能会想吃你最喜欢的派
And also, I just wanted to say that I'm sorry.
还有 我只想说一句对不起
She's in.
她进去了
Hey. What...
嘿 什么...
Sinclair, come in. Do you copy?
辛克莱尔 请回答 听到吗?
Yep, this is Sinclair. Copy. Go ahead.
是 我是辛克莱尔 听到了 请说
Sinclair, I'm confused. I thought your sister said that Tina was mean.
辛克莱尔 我很困惑 我以为你妹妹说蒂娜很刻薄
Oh, no, no. She's not mean. She's a villain.
哦 不是的 她不是刻薄 她是个反派
Kill the puppies for a fur coat kind of villain.
为了一件皮大衣 会杀死小狗的那种反派
Trust me.
相信我
How long before the drugs kick in?
药物多久会起效?
- Depends how much pie they eat. - And how fast they eat it.
- 取决于他们吃多少派 - 以及他们吃得有多快
- What they had for lunch. - Caffeine intake, alcohol intake.
- 他们几点吃的午餐、吃了什么 - 咖啡因摄入量、酒精摄入量
It's a lot of variables.
有很多变数
Yeah, what could go wrong, right?
是啊 能出什么问题 是吧?
Aside from everything.
除了一切
Aw, you know, I'm so happy you girls made up.
啊 你们知道吗? 我真高兴你们和好了
We've missed you, Erica. Haven't we, dear?
我们很想你 艾瑞卡 对吧 亲爱的?
- We missed this pie, that's for sure. - Hmm.
我们想念这个派了 这是肯定的
Now, Erica, you've done something different this time.
好了 艾瑞卡 这次你有一些不一样的做法
Sorry?
抱歉?
Your pie. It's got a little... something extra tonight.
你的派 好像... 今晚好像多加了些什么东西
A little hint of...
带有那么一点点...
Nutmeg.
肉豆蔻
Nutmeg! Of course.
肉豆蔻!当然了
Brilliant. Brilliant. Brill... Brilliant.
棒极了 棒极...了
Tina, aren't you gonna try some?
蒂娜 你不尝几口吗?
Oh, I wish. Looks super good. Just gotta watch those calories, you know.
哦 我希望我能吃 看起来很美味 但我必须要留意卡路里摄入
Fatty McFatFat.
大肥胖墩
Derek, remember what we talked about.
德瑞克 记住我们说过的话
If you don't have something nice to say, don't say it at all.
如果你没有好话要说 就别说话
This is how you alienate your spears, Derek.
你这样就会疏远你的铜板 德瑞克
My spears?
我的铜板?
Your spears. Sph... Spheres. Peers.
你的铜板、同伙、同伴
Holy shit, Dad's wasted again.
我勒个去 爸爸又喝醉了
Derek. Please, language.
德瑞克 别说脏话
Well, I used a low-fat creamer, so you can enjoy guilt-free.
我用了低脂奶精 这样你就可以毫无负担地享受了
Thanks, but I'm just not hungry.
谢了 但我不饿
But I made it for you.
我是专门为你做的
I said I'm not hungry.
我说了我不饿!
Just a bite or two.
吃一两口就好
- Okay, why are you being so weird? - What?
- 好吧 你为什么这么奇怪? - 什么?
Why do you care so much if I eat your stupid pie?
你为什么非得要我吃你愚蠢的派?
Because it's for you.
因为这是给你做的
Oh my God. It's because you want me fat, isn't it?
天啊 是因为你想让我变胖 对吧?
- Girls, please. - Why would I want you fat?
- 姑娘们 拜托 - 我为什么想让你变胖?
Because you're still jealous of me and Josh,
因为你还在吃我和乔希的醋
and you wanna sabotage our chances of being together.
你想破坏我们在一起的机会
I was never jealous of you and Josh.
我从没嫉妒过你和乔希
- Then how do you explain PE? - It was an accident.
- 那你怎么解释体育课的事? - 那是一场意外
Ken, where are you going?
肯 你要去哪里?
I'm not feeling good.
我不舒服
It wasn't an accident.
那不是意外
It was dodgeball. In dodgeball, you throw balls at people.
是躲避球 玩躲避球的时候 就会把球扔向别人
Not that hard. You gave Joshy a black eye. Now he won't even look at me.
没那么难 你把乔希眼睛打青了 现在他连看都不看我一眼了
That's stupid. You didn't throw the ball.
- 那就太蠢了 球又不是你扔的 - 不重要 他把我们联系在一起
He associates us. And you humiliated him.
他把我们联系在一起 而你羞辱了他
He humiliated himself by crying like a goddamn pussy.
他羞辱了自己 因为他哭得像个该死的娘炮
Ken?
肯?
Oh my God.
天啊
Mommy!
妈妈!
Mom.
妈
Erica, call 911! Erica!
艾瑞卡 快打911!艾瑞卡!
Mom, wake up.
妈 醒醒
Erica!
艾瑞卡!
Mommy, wake up. Daddy.
妈妈 醒醒 爸爸
Erica, I told you to call 911.
艾瑞卡 我叫你快打911
And I told you to eat your damn pie.
而我叫你把你该死的派给吃了
- This is gonna work. - It better work.
- 会成功的 - 最好成功
It's not like we're conspicuous or anything.
我们反正也没有很显眼
Hey. Talk to me, guys. How's it looking out there?
嘿 跟我说说 各位 外面的情况怎么样?
It's boring.
很无聊
How are the Turnbows holding up?
特恩鲍一家怎么样?
They're still in their "food comas," but I swear to God, this Demo better show.
还处于“吃撑后的昏迷状态” 但我向上帝发誓 这个魔王最好出现
If we took out an entire family for nothing,
如果我们白白迷晕了一家人
my conscience will never recover.
我的良心就永远无法恢复了
I thought you quit.
我以为你已经戒了
Quit what?
戒了什么?
Pretty smooth.
演得真好
Thanks.
谢谢
Where's your coat?
你的外套呢?
It's in the barn.
在谷仓里
Well, you should get it if you're gonna be out here.
如果你要站在外面 最好去把外套穿上
Mom,
妈妈
about this morning...
关于今天早上的事...
Will, it's fine.
威尔 没事的
No, no, it's not.
不 不是的
I shouldn't have talked to you that way, and I was a jerk, and I'm sorry.
我不该那样跟你说话 我表现得很混帐 我很抱歉
Honey, I'm sorry too.
亲爱的 我也很抱歉
I know I can be...
我知道我可能...
I can be a lot.
我可能会很难应付
That's not true.
不是这样的
It's just, when I couldn't find you this morning...
只是 今天早上我找不到你的时候
I don't know.
我不知道
I think about that night all the time.
我一直会想起那一晚
The night it came for you,
它找上你的那晚
the night all this started.
这一切开始的那晚
My shift ran late.
我的班拖到很晚才结束
When I finally do get home, what do I do?
等我终于回到家之后 我做了什么?
I smoke cigarettes, drink cheap wine, and watch Cheers reruns until I pass out.
我抽烟、喝劣质酒 看《欢乐酒店》重播直到昏睡过去
I didn't know you were missing for eight hours.
八个小时里 我都不知道你失踪了
Mom, what happened to me, it's not your fault.
妈 发生在我身上的事不是你的错
Eight hours.
八个小时
What kind of mother doesn't check on their 11-year-old boy?
什么样的母亲 不去关心自己11岁的儿子?
That is ridiculous!
太荒谬了!
The jury's still out on your new friend.
对于你的新朋友还没有定论
She certainly is interesting.
她确实是个有趣的人物
But one thing I know for sure,
但有一件事我很确定
she's not your mom.
她不是你妈妈
She hasn't seen what I've seen,
她没看到过我看到过的东西
and I am not gonna look away.
我不会移开视线的
Not again. Not until this is over, and you're safe.
再也不会了 直到这一切结束 直到你安全了
You don't have to look away, Mom. I... I just... I need you to trust me.
你不用移开视线 妈妈 我只是需要你相信我
I do trust you, Will.
我确实相信你 威尔
But, you know, trust is a two-way street.
但你知道 信任是双向的
Even though my plan last night kind of sucked...
即使我昨晚的计划有点糟糕...
- Kind of? - Hey!
- 只是有点糟糕? - 嘿!
Let's get your coat on.
我们去把你的外套拿来吧
It's a lot harder to save the world if you have the sniffles.
如果你流鼻涕了 拯救世界的难度就会增加
So, like, what kind of criminals does your uncle defend exactly?
你叔叔具体是为哪种犯罪分子辩护?
You know, are they, like, white-collar criminals?
是那种白领罪犯吗?
Because that does seem like a Harrington thing to do,
因为那看起来 的确像是哈林顿家的人会做的事
like, defend rich douchebags.
为有钱的混蛋辩护
And in this situation,
在这种情况下
I think that the rich douchebags would be coming for us.
我觉得那些有钱的混蛋会来对付我们
Steve?
史蒂夫?
Steve? Are you there?
史蒂夫?你在吗?
Yeah, I hear you. Just stop talking.
我听到了 你先别说话了
I think we've got company.
我觉得有动静了
Moving south down Arlington, T-minus 30 seconds.
沿着阿灵顿街向南 倒数30秒
Status check. Taggers?
状态检查 标签员?
In position and set. Launcher?
就位并准备就绪 发射员?
Set. Catcher?
准备就绪 捕手?
Set. Trackers?
准备就绪 追踪员?
Set. Let's do this thing already.
准备好了 我们赶紧行动吧
It's inside.
它在里面了
Minimize chatter.
尽可能少说话
It's inside. Keep your traps shut.
它在里面了 都把嘴给闭上
Catch this!
抓这个吧!
Get him!
打他!
Now!
现在!
Nancy!
南茜!
Nancy! Hurry! Come on!
南茜!快点 快啊!
Get him, Mike! Get him, Mike! Mike, get him! Get him!
打他 迈克!打死他 迈克! 迈克 打他!快打他!
It flipped! It flipped!
它进入颠倒世界了!进去了!
Signal acquired. Headed our way.
收到信号 朝我们这边来了
How close?
有多近?
Dustin, how close?
达斯汀 有多近?
Shit.
该死
Where is it?
它在哪里呢?
Hold your horses.
稍安勿躁
Bearing northwest and fast.
西北方向 速度很快
- Oh, come on. - Demo tagged and released.
- 哦 拜托 - 魔王已被标记并释放
Trackers in pursuit. Repeat, trackers in pursuit. Hit it!
追踪员正在追击 重复 追踪员正在追击 快走!
All right, signal holding. Just keep steady.
好的 信号稳定 稳住
Holding. Turn right.
稳定 右转
- Right? - Right! Turn right! Right now!
- 右转? - 右转!向右转!马上!
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
对不起!
Whoa! You're gonna crash!
哇!你要撞车了!
- You said right! - Jesus Christ!
- 你说了右转! - 天啊!
Stop! Stop! Stop right now! Stop here!
停下!快停车!赶紧停车!
God damn it! Henderson, what are we doing?
该死!亨德森 我们在做什么?
We lost the signal!
信号丢失了!
- Come on. Come on! - Shit, shit, shit.
- 拜托 行行好! - 该死
Shit, shit, shit.
该死
- I got it! It's headed southeast now! - God damn it.
- 搞定了 它现在往东南方向移动! - 该死
- Jesus! - Sorry!
- 天啊! - 对不起!
It's okay.
没事的
- Whoa, whoa, whoa! Shit! - Hang on!
- 哇 该死! - 抓紧了!
Shit, shit, shit!
该死!
Jesus Christ.
天啊
All right, I've got it.
好了 找到信号了
- You got it? - Yes, I got it.
- 有信号了? - 是的 找到信号了
Why would they turn around?
他们为什么掉转方向?
Maybe he's trying to shake them?
也许他是想要甩掉他们?
No, that's impossible. It doesn't know it's being tracked.
不 这不可能 它根本都不知道自己被追踪了
Stay away from me! Stay away!
离我远点!走开!
No, no, no, no, no.
不好了
I'm so, so sorry, okay?
我真的很抱歉 好吗?
I'll probably explain this at some point, but for now, don't move.
我可能之后 会给你解释 但现在你先别动
- I thought he ate, like, two slices. - He did!
- 我以为他吃了两块苹果派 - 是的!
Why is he awake then?
那他为什么醒了?
It doesn't matter.
不重要了
Not anymore.
已经不重要了
We're southeast.
我们在东南方向
That's why it turned around.
所以它才会掉转方向
Vecna's seen.
维克那看见了
He knows where we are.
他知道我们在哪里
Hello?
有人吗?
Henry?
亨利?
Are you there?
你在那里吗?
Hi.
你好